ecowas-int.org 2016-05-14

# Privacy Policy | WEBs BOOKMARKS

WebsBookmarks.info automatically recognizes a visitor’s IP address, the site referring the visitor to us, and the visitor’s browser type, as well as other browser metrics. Usage information, such as the number and frequency of visits to our website, is collected as well. This information is solely for internal use, to gauge security as well as the overall performance of our website’s software and content.

Any personal information, such as your name, phone number, e-mail address, as well as any other personally-identifying information would only be collected upon your approval with a clearly visible form that you must opt to manually fill yourself. Such information is only used to provide the visitor with announcements and services specifically requested; we will not spam or otherwise misuse your personal information.

Our website may place a ‘cookie’ in the visitor’s browser. The cookie itself will not contain personal information, but it would enable us to analyze the user’s usage of our site, in relation to other information knowingly provided to us by the user. Opting-out of the cookies delivered to your browser can be performed in your browser settings. Please be sure to follow proper instructions as altering cookies settings might change your experience on other websites. Your experience on WebsBookmarks.info should not be affected by your cookie settings.

Websbookmarks.info contains links to other sites, including ones that are owned and managed by our clients, advertisers, amongst other organizations. These websites might collect your personal information, independent of our website. Websbookmarks.info is not responsible for privacy policies, contents, or practices of websites to which we point, hyperlink, or otherwise provide access to.

Websbookmarks.info uses industry-standard procedures, physical, electronic, and administrative, to protect any information collected about our visitors, subscribers, and web browsers. The procedures intend to protect information against loss, misuse, or alteration.

Your email address, if you should provide it to Websbookmarks.info, will only be used to contact you. We will not disclose your email or personal information to any third-party organization.

**Disclaimer**

Our privacy policy, terms of service, website content and services are subject to change at our discretion and without notice. In case of transfer of website ownership, it is the new owner’s responsibility to adhere to this Privacy Policy and/or edit it to suit any new/omitted website services, practices, and policies.

**Contact Us**
